[{"answer": "It's such a tragedy really the way that things have unfolded in Iraq.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "What is your take?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it needs to be substantiated if those chemical weapons were, in fact, used.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "How significant is this, do you think?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, let's put this into context.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 55, "question": "And if turns out Assad has got them and has used them against the rebels, what is the proportionate reaction should come from America?", "qSentId": 54}, {"answer": "Well, you start by not believing the people who lied to you before.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How do we know who to believe here?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "You're talking about Obama versus Bush?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "What it is is -- first of all we set this thing up to where we supported the Shiites and the Sunnis are now -- there is going to be a version of a civil war.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "It's a bit late, isn't it?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "But -- how -- if you get a war wrong what are the repercussions?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "Well, I have so many things to say we don't have time to cover them all.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "What was your reaction?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "I have repeatedly asked him.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "He won't come on here?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "People are going to have to let these politicians know that they're going to be voted out in the next term.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "What can they do if their politicians are simply too cowardly to act on their behalf because of the power of the NRA?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, I think we all know the answer to that question.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "In other words, it was right home to them and their families?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Well, your people, your producers have called me since Aurora.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Michael, why the change of mind?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "Where are the people who -- as Robert Kennedy brilliantly said, where is this -- the moral leadership?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Rachel Maddow.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Which show is that?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "So you do DVR the show?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "There is a ton of money being made right now.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "What is wrong with people?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "There is only one answer.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "What's the answer, Michael?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "I wonder -- I would ask that to Harry Reid.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "The next school?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "I want him to explain himself.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "How about 1,050 children?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 675, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 674}, {"answer": "Well, growing up in our house, Francis of Assisi was like -- you know, he was right up there with the Virgin Mary because of what he stood for, his concern for the poor, environment.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "He has -- well, let me -- I want to be optimistic right now.", "docId": "130319pmt", "aSentId": 684, "question": "What do you want to say about the new Pope?", "qSentId": 683}]